Contact

neginshahany@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/negin-banay-shahani-7180ab19a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Front-end Development React.js java

Languages

Korean (Elementary)
Persian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Hadoop Platform and Application Framework

ICPCID

React JS

CSS

HTML

Negin Banay Shahani

Student at Guilan University

Langarud County

Summary

I started learning web development from two years ago and I learned HTML, css, bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, SQL server and a bit of PHP. Also interested in Network Security and eager to learn new things about it. I'm currently learning about Big data and its platforms such as Hadoop and Spark too.

I seek for hardships anywhere because i want to test my power every single day .I love teaching and did a lot of teaching assistant things in the last year as you can see. simply A hard-working student who love to learn more :)

Experience

University of Guilan 1 year 5 months

Microprocessor and assembly language Teaching Assistant September 2020 - January 2021 (5 months)

Guilan, Iran

Instructor: Dr. HamidReza Ahmadifar

I was responsible to help students with their homework, assessed their assignments and final projects.

Computer Architecture Teaching Assistant February 2020 - August 2020 (7 months)

Guilan, Iran

Instructor: Dr. HamidReza Ahmadifar

My main responsibility was to assessing the students' assignments and their final projects. Also I have to answer students' question online because of Coronavirus pandemic.

Microprocessor and assembly language Teaching Assistant February 2020 - August 2020 (7 months)

Guilan, Iran

Instructor: Dr. HamidReza Ahmadifar

I was responsible to help students with their homework, assessing their assignments and final projects.

Theory of formal languages and Automata Teaching Assistant February 2020 - August 2020 (7 months)

Guilan ,Iran

Instructor: Dr. S.M.Shekarian

I was responsible to make a presentation of what student should know for each new subject and answer their questions online because of Coronavirus pandemic. Every two week I made a homework assignment for students based on "An Introduction to Formal Languages and Automata" book from Peter Linz and assessing students' assignments too.

Digital Circuits Teaching Assistant September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months)

Guilan, Iran

Instructor: Dr. Mahdi Aminian

My job was to hold weekly sessions, Solve sample questions and assessing the students' assignments and their final projects.

Education

Guilan University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (2017 - 2021)